<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on BSidesTLV 2020</title>
    <link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on BSidesTLV 2020</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bsidestlv.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call For Paper</title>
      <link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/cfp/</guid>
      <description>DevFest Toulouse will take place on October 3rd, 2019 at Pierre Baudis congress center. Our fourth edition will gather 1000 attendees!
While waiting for the D-day do not hesitate to propose a talk at DevFest Toulouse CFP. It is now open and this year it will be for 2 months only (from March the 25th to Mai the 25th.)
Be aware that at mid terms, we will select our “early speakers”, so do not wait till the end!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CTF</title>
      <link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/ctf/</guid>
      <description>Hall of Fame ##2018
Honorable Mention: @doadam – Adam Donenfeld
1st place: reclass (Nir Lavi and Intel’s team)
2nd place: babyr00t (known also as dm0n)
3rd place : JCTF (@schturdel, @nmontag, @YaakovCohen88 and Israel Erlich)
2018 CTF One of our volunteers was kind enough to deliver a care package to the person who solved everything first! (Adam Donenfeld) – while not eligeble to win, he did solve everything first. 2018 Challenges    # Challenge Author     1 IAmBrute Tomer Zait and Nimrod Levy   2 Redirect me Tomer Zait and Nimrod Levy   3 IH8emacs Tomer Zait and Nimrod Levy   4 I’m Pickle Rick!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Ground</title>
      <link>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bsidestlv.com/blog/hiring_ground/</guid>
      <description>BSidesTLV 2019 Hiring Ground - 24.6 10:00-16:00 This is the first year we are doing our BSidesTLV “Hiring Ground”. We are doing our best to have a wonderful event, but please make allowances for any mistakes we might make. Our hope is that this part of the event will be focused on helping members of our community find their next positions, and connect them with potential employers.
Agenda The hiring ground will operate at the 24.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>